Hola, nerd-migos.
(Penny:)Why do you people hate sleep?
(Penny:)Are you wearing my robe?
(Howard:)Oh, yeah. Sorry, I'll have it cleaned.
(Penny:)That's okay, keep it.
- Where's Christy?
- In the shower.
(Howard:)By the way,
where did you get that loofah mitt?
(Howard:)Yours reaches places
that mine just won't.
(Penny:)You used my loofah?
(Howard:)More precisely, we used your loofah.
(Howard:)I exfoliated her brains out.
(Penny:)You can keep that too.
(Howard:)Ah. Well, then, we'll probably need to talk
about your stuffed-bear collection.
CHRISTY: Howard?
- In here, milady.
(Christie(entering):)Mm. There's my little engine that could.
[IMITATING TRAIN]
(Sheldon:)There's one beloved children's book
I'll never read again.